<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ana Nora Evans</title>
    <link>//ananoraevans.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ana Nora Evans</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//ananoraevans.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ana Nora Evans</title>
      <link>//ananoraevans.org/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//ananoraevans.org/main/</guid>
      <description>Ana Nora (Sovarel) Evans 
University of Virginia
AnaNEvans@virginia.edu   Research &amp;nbsp &amp;middot; &amp;nbsp Teaching &amp;nbsp &amp;middot; &amp;nbsp Other Activities &amp;nbsp &amp;middot; &amp;nbsp Personal  I am currently enrolled in the Post Graduate Master of Teaching program at the School of Education and Human Development at the University of Virginia, to earn a teaching licence for secondary education in Mathematics and Computer Science.
I am looking for a teaching position in secondary education in Mathematics or Computer Science starting with the 2022-2023 school year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elementary School Math Lessons</title>
      <link>//ananoraevans.org/secondgrademath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//ananoraevans.org/secondgrademath/</guid>
      <description>In Spring 2020, I developed and delivered online guest lectures for a group of second graders.
We started with a lesson in formulas for areas. We used cuting and rearranging methods to deduce the formulas for area of rectangles, parallelograms and triangles ([pptx], [Video]).
We continued our exploration of geometry with the Pythagorean theorem. We explored a cut and rearrange proof ([pptx]).
We concluded our explorations with the construction of natural numbers based on Peano&amp;rsquo;s Axioms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Application Materials</title>
      <link>//ananoraevans.org/job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//ananoraevans.org/job/</guid>
      <description>I am looking for a teaching position in the Charlotetsville-Albemarle area in a middle school or high school.
After graduation in May 2022, I will earn a Virginia teaching licence for secondary Mathematics education, with an endorsement in Computer Science. Because I hold a Master in Computer Science and a Master of Arts in Mathematics degrees, I am also qualified to teach dual-enrollment classes.
Job application materials:
  CV</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
